<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>THE HEAP on The Heap</title>
    <link>https://theheap.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in THE HEAP on The Heap</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>THE HEAP</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 18:24:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theheap.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection: Emojion Bar</title>
      <link>https://theheap.us/article/heap_reflection_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 18:24:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theheap.us/article/heap_reflection_01/</guid>
      <description>Summary A post to discuss and reflect some thoughts on running a The Heap project for the first time.
The TL;DR / Shortlist of things I hope to expand on in this post are the following:
 This project perhaps too ambitious by having three components (ie three different programming terminology) Naming things is hard. I should have pointers to resources for complete beginners &amp;ndash; setting up a dev environment, contributing on github/using git.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emojion Bar</title>
      <link>https://theheap.us/project/17_05_emojion_bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 20:26:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theheap.us/project/17_05_emojion_bar/</guid>
      <description> Current Status This project is currently in planning stages. It will become open to contribution for the month of May 2017.
Links et. al  Repository Youtube Playlist  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://theheap.us/page/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 19:20:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theheap.us/page/faq/</guid>
      <description>Q: Are these projects courses?
A: No
Q: Do I have to pay $$$ ?
A: No. This is FREEEEEEE.
Q: Why didn&amp;rsquo;t you respond to my PR or issue?
A: There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance you didn&amp;rsquo;t read the readme, contribution guidelines, or read the project roadmap. Many projects will be taking place over a short window of time and so there will not always be time to get a project done if dealing with contributions that (majorly) deviate from the purpose / goals or general roadmap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://theheap.us/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 14:09:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theheap.us/page/about/</guid>
      <description>The Heap from 10,000 Feet The Heap runs open source projects. Anyone can join and collaborate.
Beyond facilitiating open source development, The Heap hopes to highlight the unique, creative, and hard work that other people in the open source community create.
Ideally this is a portal that springboards into a world of content creation (open source projects ) and content consumption (podcasts, articles, and thought pieces on programming and open source creation).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>