<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on The Heap</title>
    <link>https://the-heap.github.io/page/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on The Heap</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>THE HEAP</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 19:20:11 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://the-heap.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://the-heap.github.io/page/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 19:20:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-heap.github.io/page/faq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are these projects courses?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do I have to pay &lt;code&gt;$$$&lt;/code&gt; ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: No. This is FREEEEEEE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why didn&amp;rsquo;t you respond to my PR or issue?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance you didn&amp;rsquo;t read the readme, contribution guidelines, or read the project roadmap. Many projects will be taking place over a short window of time and so there will not always be time to get a project done if dealing with contributions that (majorly) deviate from the purpose / goals or general roadmap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How come projects are only worked on for &lt;code&gt;X&lt;/code&gt; amount of time?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: First off, projects can continually be worked on for as long as they are here, hosted on &lt;code&gt;The Heap&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;em&gt;However&lt;/em&gt;, the current initiative of The Heap Projects, is to get a project done, within a window of time. Deadlines make things happen. The purpose here is to &lt;em&gt;focus&lt;/em&gt; on a single project by imposing restrictions — in this case time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can I keep working or contributing to this after the time window is up?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Yes, but there is no promise that the maintainer of the project (The Heapmaster) will continue to maintain the project. You may be wasting your time creating issues or PR&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; the participants have moved on in their lives to other greater things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why did/didn&amp;rsquo;t you choose &lt;code&gt;X&lt;/code&gt; tool or &lt;code&gt;Y&lt;/code&gt; library for &lt;code&gt;Z&lt;/code&gt; project?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: It could be that I chose to build things a certain way out of interest to try new tools, get away from tools. The main goal, is to keep things simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why are you focused on keeping things simple?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Because I believe you need to work simply / do the dumbest thing first to get things done. As developers, (I at least) I think we&amp;rsquo;re susceptible to over engineering, pre-optimizing, nerd-sniping etc. Simplicity, and boring methodologies sometimes are best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who&amp;rsquo;s running the show here?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/teesloane/&#34;&gt;This guy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to work on your project; your idea is dumb.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: That&amp;rsquo;s not a question!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://the-heap.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 14:09:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-heap.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-heap-from-10-000-feet&#34;&gt;The Heap from 10,000 Feet&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Heap runs open source projects. Anyone can join and collaborate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond facilitiating open source development, The Heap hopes to highlight the unique, creative, and hard work that other people in the open source community create.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideally this is a portal that springboards into a world of content creation (open source projects ) and content consumption (podcasts, articles, and thought pieces on programming and open source creation).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;values&#34;&gt;Values&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Heap as an &lt;em&gt;entity&lt;/em&gt; has some high hopes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In Coding and Collaboration&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating a welcoming space for people of all skills, abilities, and backgrounds to hack on things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To keep things as simple as possible to get things done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To make and learn together&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the OSS world at large&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Looking at cool shit other people have made and discussing / trying to understand how it was built.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spreading the love for open source.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions, please check out the &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/page/faq&#34;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>